(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
人を過度に信じないように
I try not to have too much faith in people
愛さないように期待しないように
Not to love too much, not to expect too much
かと言って角が立たないように
On the other hand, I try not to cause offense
気取らぬように 目立たぬように
Not to act high-and-mighty, not to stand out
誰一人傷つけぬように
I try not to hurt anyone
虐めぬように 殺さぬように
Not to bully anyone, not to kill anyone
かと言って偽善がバレないように
On the other hand, don't let hypocrisy be revealed
威張らないように
Not to act superior
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
And don't forget light jokes and lip service
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
I try to smile and charm everyone at all times
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
兎角言わずにたんと召し上がれ
Eat up, don't ask questions, just have some
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You have to fix your fussy eating habits properly
頭空っぽその後に残る心が
If the heart left when your head is empty...
本物なら
...is the real thing
きっと君だって同じ事
Then I'm sure you'd do the same thing
さぁ ここらで一つ
Well, now here's one...
や、や、や、や、や、嫌
N-n-n-n-n-no
人を信用しないように
I do my best not to trust people too much
人を愛さないように
Not to love anyone
期待しないように
Not to expect too much
その一方で、嫌われないように
On the other hand, I try not to cause offense
偉そうにしないように
Not to act all haughty
反感を買わないように
Not to draw in any hate
冗談を言って、愛想を振りまいて
I also mustn't forget to throw in a light joke
都合よく笑って
And some smooth talk here and there
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
全部食べて、黙ってろ
Just eat it all, and don't say a word
孤独な愛は汚れる
Sometimes, lonely love makes you dirty
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
明日もその先も
Surely tomorrow and beyond
地獄は続く
Hell will continue endlessly
信者さん、収支計はいかが？
Believers, how is the balance sheet?
ヘコラヘコラ言っちゃって
Bowing and scraping, just saying...
あれ？前髪超絶最強じゃん！
Wait, isn't your fringe the ultimate best?
とか、どうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Even though it doesn't matter, just saying it...
マイマイ、もう限界！
Dancing around, already at the limit!
宗教的社会の集団です
It's a group in a cult-like society
決して発狂しないように
Let's make sure we don't go crazy
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
ときに孤独な愛は君も汚す
Sometimes lonely love will dirty you too
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
飾り立てた後味、苦さの後
The decorated aftertaste, after the bitterness...
初めはあんなに大層な
At first, it was so grand
大義名分を並べたが
Lining up those noble pretexts
いや、嫌、嫌、もう好きな文字
No, no, no, just whatever words I like
言えやしないし、教えやしない
I can't say them, I won't teach them
毒は吐き出し、媚を売って
Spitting out poison and selling favors
君、センスあるよ
You've got some sense
恋しちゃって、気取っちゃって
Falling in love, putting on airs
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
恋しちゃって、気取っちゃって
Falling in love, putting on airs
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
F U C K Y O U
F-U-C-K-Y-O-U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Yearning for the ideal everyone wants
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
個性や情を全部焼き払い
Burning away all individuality and emotion
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Killing desire and ego and burying them in the earth
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter chocolate decoration
僕は大人にやっと成ったよ、ママ
I finally became an adult, Mom
明日もその先も
Surely tomorrow and beyond
地獄は続く、どこまでも
Hell will continue endlessly, everywhere
あぁ、だからさ、今は
Ah, that's why, please, just for now
子供の頃の気持ちのままでいよう
Let's stay with our childhood feelings
余計なことは忘れてさ
Forgetting unnecessary things
あぁ、思い出した！
Ah, I remembered!
あの時の君、真面目な顔してたな
You, at that time, looking so serious
や、や、や、や、嫌
N-n-n-n-n-no
サイコロ...
A dice...
5が出た
I rolled a five
何これ？
Hmm? What's this?
椅子？
A chair?
One, two, one
アップダウンは世の常
Rising and falling is pretty normal in this world
クズ引いたって動じない
Even if I draw a bad hand, I won't let it show
肝心なの Strong な Mind
It's very important to have a strong mind
出し抜いて Survive
Outsmart them, survive
行きつく先は Heaven or hell
Where we end up is heaven or hell
この世の...
This world...
Deal with the devil
見透かして
I see right through
裏返して あたしのモノにする
Flip the cards, I'll make them mine
あんたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single one of your hairs, everything
A million dollars, I'd say raise
さあ come on 覚悟決めて
Come on, prepare yourself
震えたかぶれ my heart
Tremble with my heart
虚勢でしょそれ You doubt me
It's just a bluff, isn't it? You doubt me
読み切って レッツ Showdown
Read it all, let's showdown
Deal with the devil
見逃さない どんな小さなズルだって
I won't miss even the smallest cheat
あたしの目はごまかされないわ
My eyes won't be deceived
A million dollars, I'd say raise
勝った相手は骨まで
I'll love the winner to the bone
愛しつくしてあげる
I'll love them with all I have
あんたの内側は
What's inside of you...
ほら見せて
Go ahead and show me
Deal with the devil
Uhhhhnn...
興奮たまらないわ スリル
The excitement, I can't stand the thrill
誰にも触らせない このmoney
I won't let anyone touch this money
A million dollars
I'd say raise
さあ come on 覚悟決めて
Come on, make up your mind
震え高ぶれ My heart
Shake, be excited, my heart
欲しがるようじゃね まだベイビー
If you want it, you're not ready yet, baby
誰にも負けない 感じさせて Love me honey
I won't lose to anyone, let me feel it, love me honey
透かし過ぎて You dummy
Seeing through everything, you dummy
読み切ったわ レッスン
I've read through it all, lesson
見栄を張って 演じきらなきゃね
Putting on a show, you have to play the part
どんな小さな 嘘だって
No matter how small the lie
私の方が見逃さないわ
I won't let it escape my sight
I'm the gambler アイ・ゲット・ザ・レイズ
I'm the gambler, I get the raise
駆け引きの相手は ごめんね
Sorry to the one I'm playing against
私が決めてあげる
I'll be the one to decide it all
狙った獲物は 逃がさない
I won't let my targeted prey get away
唇濡らして いただきます My fate
Wetting my lips, I'll take it—my fate
ダイヤのジャックで 手が揃うわ
With the Jack of Diamonds, I've got my hand
笑みは殺して 待つだけ
Kill your smile and just wait
私のポーカーフェイスはパーフェクト
My poker face is perfect
一部の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show even the slightest opening
視線感じて You're the one
Feeling your gaze, you're the one
お遊びは 最後まで
The game continues until the very end
見てるばかりじゃ 嫌いよ
I hate just being watched
私が欲しくてたまらない？
Do you want me so badly?
負けるのは怖い？ ヨロシク
Afraid to lose? Nice to meet you
読み切ったわ レッスン
I've read through it all, lesson
見栄を張って 演じきらなきゃね
Putting on a show, you have to play the part
私のモノにするわ あなたの髪の1本まで全部
I'll make you mine, down to every single hair on your head
I'm the gambler アイ・ゲット・ザ・レイズ
I'm the gambler, I get the raise
震えているのよ 坊や
You're shaking, aren't you, boy?
どこまでも行くわ
I'll go as far as it takes
見栄を張って 演じきらなきゃね
Putting on a show, you have to play the part
ためらわないで 触れて
Don't hesitate, touch me
誰にも触らせない このmoney
I won't let anyone touch this money
I'm the gambler アイ・ゲット・ザ・レイズ
I'm the gambler, I get the raise
さあ come on 覚悟決めて
Come on, make up your mind
灰になるまで 打って
Play until you turn to ash
欲しがるようじゃね まだベイビー
If you want it, you're not ready yet, baby
誰にも負けない 感じさせて Love me honey
I won't lose to anyone, let me feel it, love me honey
あれ？ 椅子なくなっちゃった。
Wait, the chairs are gone.
あー、もう少し座らせてほしかった。
Ah, I wanted to sit for a little longer.
はい、みんな！ 見えてる？ 聞こえてる？
Hey everyone! Can you see me? Hear me?
ホロライブ所属の癒し系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！
I'm Hololive's healing half-elf, Akirose, a.k.a. Aki Rosenthal!
ハローハローハロー！ アローナ！
Hello, hello, hello! Aloha!
えー、今回のアキロゼ生誕祭2026へようこそ！
Well, welcome to this Akirose Birthday Celebration 2026!
早速ね、なんかいろいろ行われていたんですが、
Right away, various things were happening, but...
一体今回のライブはどうなっちゃうのか、
what exactly is going to happen in this live?
ぜひ最後まで必戦、お見逃しなくお願いします。
Please make sure to watch until the very end, don't miss it.
今回のライブのハッシュタグは「#アキロゼ生誕祭2026」
The hashtag for this live is '#AkiroseBirthdayCelebration2026'.
こちらをつけて、Xにたくさんポストしてね！
Please use it to post a lot on X!
もちろん可愛いスクショ、絵もたくさん撮って、
Of course, take lots of cute screenshots and drawings,
合わせて投稿してください。
and post them together.
ライブが終わった後、アキロゼ見に行きます！
After the live, I, Akirose, will go take a look!
見てねー！ あ、チャンネル登録もよろしくね！
Check it out! Oh, and please subscribe to the channel too!
OK？ 特撮撮って？
OK? Did you get the shot?
はい、ありがとう！
Alright, thank you!
お、お？ なんだ？ なになになに？
Oh, oh? What's this? What's going on?
うーん、っていうかここどこなんだろう？
Hmm, and I wonder where this place is?
おぉー！ あんなとこにルーレットがある！
Whoa! There's a roulette wheel over there!
え？ 回るのかな？
Eh? Will it spin?
まー まー 回った！ え、すごい！ 回った！
It- It- It's spinning! Oh, wow! It spun!
なに？なに？
What? What is it?
どうなっちゃうの？
What's going to happen?
ピース？
Peace?
ん？なんだ？
Hm? What is it?
Unhappy? 悩める人の子よ
Unhappy? You troubled child
Unlucky? 人成らざる者も
Unlucky? Including you who are not human
Be happy! 弛まず目指せよ
Be happy! Aim tirelessly
アンデッド！生きているんだし
UNDEAD! You are alive, right?
目を逸らした過去も
Even the past you turned your eyes away from
退屈な未来も
And the boring future
カウンセリング やれやれ
Counseling you, oh my, oh my
古今東西 Peace, Peace, yeah!
Universal, peace, peace, yeah!
UNDEAD
ねぇねぇねぇ なんだかどうして 戦ってるようなそんな気がするの
Hey, hey, hey, I feel like I'm fighting for some reason
逃げ出せない 痛くもない 孤高の自分
Can't escape, not even hurting, my solitary self
とうの昔に死んでる 透明な亡霊対決
Died long ago, a battle of transparent ghosts
痛いっけ？痛い記憶の奥
Does it hurt? Deep within painful memories
残念 もういないのに
Too bad, you're not here anymore
あれ？ そっちがアイロニー
Huh? That's the irony
透かされてるのは 今の自分
The one being seen through is my current self
ナンセンス 消えないヘテロ 卑怯 コンプレックス
Nonsense, unerased hetero, cowardly complex
取り憑かれてるみたい 巻き付いたまま
Like I'm possessed, still coiled around
まだ 離れない ありし日の自分 アンデッド
Still won't leave, my former self, UNDEAD
信じられない お前と私の連鎖
Unbelievable, the chain between you and me
生きてることが 問いかけ続ける形
Being alive is a form of constant questioning
空想に甘んじて 満足するなよ
Don't be content and satisfied with fantasies
幸せになろうとしないなんて 嫌だ
I hate the idea of not trying to be happy
この世 この世は奇奇怪怪 ファンタジー
This world, this world is a bizarre fantasy
次は 鬼が出るか 蛇が出るか
Next, will it be a demon or a snake?
会って 会って やっと始まる物語
Meeting, meeting, the story finally begins
先手 完敗 化けの皮 その九大 Peace, Peace
Preemptive total defeat, the mask slips, those 9 pieces Peace, Peace
ねぇ なんだかどうして 未来になんてさの
Hey, somehow why, towards the future
淡い期待のような気がして
I feel like it's a faint hope
もう随分生きてる 意地張ったテンプレート食傷
Lived for quite a while, fed up with stubborn templates
奇跡なんて 出来事の気配もない
No sign of anything like a miracle
残念 全て経験因果 形骸化した 私は退屈の進化
Too bad, all experience and karma, I'm fossilized boredom
今日は刺激を頂戴 飽きちゃった 誰か頂戴
Give me some stimulation today, I'm bored, someone give me something
何千回も解いていく ガイダンス セルフコンプライアンス
Solving guidance and self-compliance thousands of times
穿たれていくみたい 吸い尽くして
Like I'm being pierced, suck it all dry
あれも これも どれも 同じ味がする アンデッド
That, this, and that, they all taste the same, UNDEAD
信じられない お前と私の連鎖
Unbelievable, the chain between you and me
いつの世の 過去も未来も 今にあるんだ
The past and future of any era exist in the now
生きていることを 愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill the act of being alive with simple honesty
目指せ ハッピーエンド アンデッド
Aim for a happy ending, UNDEAD
信じられない お前に見せてるんだ 幸せを
Unbelievable, I'm showing you happiness
諦めてしまうな 人であれ
Don't give up, remain human
ただ苦しみに慣れて 耐えているだけじゃ
If you're just used to suffering and enduring it
死んでるも同然 屍のアンデッド
You're as good as dead, a corpse-like UNDEAD
Unhappy? 悩める人の子よ
Unhappy? You troubled child
Unlucky? 人成らざる者も
Unlucky? Including you who are not human
Be happy! 弛まず目指せよ
Be happy! Aim tirelessly
生きているんだろう
You are alive, right?
不条理に浸るも 幸せになるのも
Whether soaking in absurdity or becoming happy
全部全部お前だ 古今東西 止まれば Peace, Peace
It's all you, universal, if it stops, Peace, Peace
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai♡Scream!
教えてもっと、あなたのことを
Teach me more, I want to know all about you
愛、愛、愛、愛... 愛♡スクリ～ム！
Ai, Ai, Ai, Ai... Ai♡Scream!
聞かせてもっと、あなたの声
Let me hear more, the sound of your voice
愛、愛、愛、愛... 愛♡スクリ～ム！
Ai, Ai, Ai, Ai... Ai♡Scream!
こんなにドキドキ もう大好きにない
My heart's pounding so much, I can't love you any more
I need you I need you
友達は卒業 運命の私
Graduating from being friends, my destiny
見つけてほしいな
I want you to find me
勇気を出して
Give it some courage
見つめる作戦
The staring operation
見つめ合えば
If we gaze at each other...
フォーリンラブ
Fall in love
止められない
Can't stop it
イェイ イェイ イェイ この恋 この愛で
Yea yea yea, with this love, with this affection
めっめっめっ 溶けちゃうよ
Me-me-me, I'm gonna melt
ねっねっねっ 気づいて マイダーリン
Hey, hey, hey, notice me my darling
とろける大好き
Melting love
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミントよりも あなた！
More than chocolate mint, I like you!
メルちゃん！
Mel-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
シチリアベリーフレーバーよりも あなた！
More than Sicily berry flavor, I like you!
チョコちゃん！
Choco-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりも あなた！
More than cookies & cream, I like you!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き アイスクリーム！
Of course I love ice cream!
止められない イェイ イェイ イェイ この恋 この愛で
Can't stop it, yea yea yea, with this love, with this affection
めっめっめっ 溶けちゃうよ
Me-me-me, I'm gonna melt
ねっねっねっ 気づいて マイダーリン
Hey, hey, hey, notice me my darling
とろける大好き
Melting love
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
お願い見つけて マイダーリン
Please find me, my darling
お願い気づいて マイダーリン
Please notice me, my darling
勇気を出して
Give it some courage
近づく作戦
The approaching operation
急上昇が触れて
The rapid rise touches...
フォーリンラブ
Fall in love
止められない イェイ イェイ イェイ この恋 この愛で
Can't stop it, yea yea yea, with this love, with this affection
めっめっめっ 溶けちゃうよ
Me-me-me, I'm gonna melt
ねっねっねっ 気づいて マイダーリン
Hey, hey, hey, notice me my darling
それはあなた
That's you
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
アイアイ アイスクリーム アイスを叫びましょう
Eye-eye ice cream, let's scream for ice cream
スクリーム アイスクリーム
Scream ice cream
おっ！ 元気もらえて面白くってオレンジで
Oh! Being cheered up, having fun, with Orange...
シャンパンコール得意な人いないかな？
Isn't there anyone good at champagne calls?
それ俺やないかーい！
That's me!
イケナイ太陽！
Forbidden Sun!
Na Na Na...
ちょっといいか見せてくれないか
Hey, can I see it?
お前のセクシーフェロモンで
With your sexy pheromones...
俺メロメロ
I'm head over heels
痺れちゃいそうでもいけないの
I feel like I'm gonna be numbed, but it's forbidden
徐々に高鳴る鼓動止められないわ
My gradually increasing heartbeat, I can't stop it
交わす言葉の記憶解く
The memories of the words we exchanged unravel
口もと 動きに揺れ動く
My lips, swaying with the movement
濡れた髪を撫でた
I stroked your wet hair
そして Ah...
And then, ah...
ABC 続かない
ABC, it doesn't continue
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
It's no good like that, is it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない？
Cause the depths of your heart are different, aren't they?
俺の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to go all the way in the heat
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's got to be you, no one else will do
俺はイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
赤い糸なんて空事
A red thread of fate is just a fabrication
でも下心でさえ信じたいな
But I want to believe even in ulterior motives
俺は正しい 君も正しい
I'm right, you're right
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
Anyway, I won't be swayed anymore
騙し騙され胸うずく
Deceiving and being deceived, my chest aches
お芝居がより盛り上げるよ
The acting will liven things up even more
息が耳に触れた二人
Our breaths touched our ears, the two of us
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC, it doesn't continue. It's no good like that, is it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない？
Cause the depths of your heart are different, aren't they?
私の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to go all the way in the heat
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's got to be you, no one else will do
私はイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
交わす言葉の記憶遠く
Memories of the words we exchanged are far away
口元の動きに揺れ動く
Trembling at the movement of your lips
濡れた髪を撫でた
I stroked your wet hair
そして Ah...
And then, ah...
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC, it doesn't continue. It's no good like that, is it?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない？
Cause the depths of your heart are different, aren't they?
俺たちの青春そんなもんじゃない
Our youth isn't something like that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to go all the way in the heat
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's got to be you, no one else will do
俺はイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
絡み合う糸は君と
The intertwining threads are with you
俺を結ぶ赤い糸
The red thread that binds me
ということで、お友達が来てくれたので
So, since friends have come,
せっかくなので自己紹介してもらおうと思います！
I'd like to have them introduce themselves!
まずは、ぷるるんちゃんから！
First, from Pururun-chan!
はーい！おはぷる！
Hi! Oha-Puru!
天使と悪魔のハーフ、ぷるぷるエンジェルデビル、甘宮ぷるるです！
Half angel, half devil, Puru Puru Angel Devil, Amamiya Pururu!
悪魔じゃー！お誕生日おめでとうー！
I'm a devil! Happy birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
とっても楽しかったー！
It was so much fun!
続いて、カルビちゃん！
Next up, Karubi-chan!
はい！お肉の国のお姫様、赤見かるびです！
Yes! Princess of the country of meat, Akami Karubi!
アキの正室、誕生日おめでとう！
Aki's legal wife, happy birthday!
ありがとう！正室...
Thank you! Legal wife...
いいライブだね、友達とライブ初めてだからさ
A great live show! It's my first time performing with friends,
マジで嬉しかったよ。ありがとう、呼んでくれて。
so I was really happy. Thanks for inviting me.
またやろうぜ！
Let's do it again!
そして最後に、ずずさん！
And finally, Zuzu-san!
はい！僕のこと知らない人いると思うんで自己紹介だけさせてください！
Yes! I think there are people who don't know me, so let me just introduce myself!
雨降ってザーザー、症状自体はジジイ
The rain falls heavily, my symptoms are like an old man's,
俺の名前はずずずず、ずずでございます！
my name is Zu-zu-zu-zu, Zuzu!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
わー早っ！
Whoa, that was fast!
お忙しい人気者だ
She's a busy popular person.
お忙しいわ！
I'm busy!
アキロゼ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Akirose, happy birthday!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Happy birthday! Happy birthday!
ありがとう！キャプ美ありがとう！
Thank you! Thanks, Cap-mi!
みんな、ありがとうー！
Thank you, everyone!
あー、賑やかで楽しかった…
Ah, it was so lively and fun...
JANE DOE
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It's as if we were the only two left in this world
なんて少しだけ夢をみてしまっただけ
I just couldn't resist dreaming for a bit
つま先に月明かり 花束の香り
Moonlight on my tiptoes, the scent of a bouquet
指に触れる指
Fingers touching fingers
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I have to go now
何もかも忘れて
Forget everything
硝子の上を裸足のまま歩く
I walk on glass, barefoot
痛むごとに 血が流れて 落ちていく
With every step, blood flows and falls
お願い その赤い足跡を
Please, follow those red footprints
たどって 会いに来て
And come find me
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
A goldfish released into a rusty pool
靴箱の中に隠したリンゴ
An apple hidden inside a shoebox
しなびた君の肌にぬかるみ
Slush on your withered skin
傷跡 犬のように泳いだ迷子
Like a scar, a lost child swimming like a dog
どこにいるよ
Where are you?
何をしてるの
What are you doing?
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes
そばにいたよ
I was by your side
遊びに行こうよ
Let's go play
どこにいるの
Where are you?
硝子の上を裸足のまま歩く
I walk on glass, barefoot
痛むごとに 血が流れて 落ちていく
With every step, blood flows and falls
お願い その赤い足跡を
Please, follow those red footprints
たどって 会いに来て
And come find me
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It's as if we were the only two left in this world
なんて少しだけ夢をみてしまっただけ
I just couldn't resist dreaming for a bit
さあ、選択の時だ
Now, it's time to choose.
コイン？
A coin?
このコインは…
This coin is...
ははっ。そうか。君はそっちなんだね。
Haha. I see. So you're one of those.
そっち？
Those?
ここに座って。
Sit here.
えっ？
Eh?
この後は君次第だよ。
After this, it's up to you.
Whisper Whisper Whisper
作詞・作曲：Azari
Lyrics & Composition: Azari
忘れられないのは この目のせい
It's these eyes' fault that I can't forget
赤く残る過ち 甘噛みの跡
The red stains of my errors, the remains of a bite
溢れだす愛は 止めどもない
The overflowing love is endless
誰もいない間に 悪魔を探す
Searching for the devil while no one is around
作り笑いは この耳のせい
It's these ears' fault for the fake smile
深い壁の中から 呼びかける声
The voice calling out from inside deep walls
Whisper, whisper, whisper
まだ触らせない
It still won't let me touch
この檻を抜け出して
I'll escape from this cage
悪魔は駆ける
And the devil will run
鏡の前で
In front of the mirror
この口のせい
Because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
The night where I suppress even my words
Whisper, whisper, whisper
まだ打ち明けない
It hasn't made it clear yet
神様を裏切って 悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God and living with demons
曖昧に夢見ていたい
I want to dream vaguely
そっと気づかせてあげたいだけ
I just want you to notice
Oh あなたにも
Oh, to you too
消えない傷を隠したい
I want to hide the scars that won't go away
あなたに そっと悩ませてあげたいだけ
I just want to make you worry a little
Oh あなたにも
Oh, to you too
悪魔を探す
Searching for the devil
作り笑いは この耳のせい
It's these ears' fault for the fake smile
深い壁の中から 呼びかける声
The voice calling out from inside deep walls
Whisper, whisper, whisper
まだ触らせない
It still won't let me touch
この檻を抜け出して
I'll escape from this cage
悪魔は駆ける
And the devil will run
鏡の前で
In front of the mirror
この口のせい
Because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
The night where I suppress even my words
Whisper, whisper, whisper
まだ打ち明けない
It hasn't made it clear yet
神様を裏切って 悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God and living with demons
BANG!!!
作詞：ryo (supercell) 作曲：Giga
Lyrics: ryo (supercell) / Composition: Giga
好き 嫌い 常識 I don't care
Like it, hate it, common sense, I don't care
吹っ飛べ BANG!!!
Blow it up with a BANG!!!
かかってこい Majority
Bring it on, majority
あたしに負けはなし
There's no such thing as losing for me
ここまでって引かれた
"That's enough" - that boundary drawn
そのボーダー 誰のルール？
Whose rule is that border?
あの日乗り越えた Weak heart
The weak heart I overcame that day
強くなったあたしが笑い飛ばしてあげる HAHA
The stronger me will just laugh it away, HAHA
言いたい事は言う
I'll say what I want to say
やりたくない事はしない
I won't do what I don't want to do
悪役(あくえき)気にしない
I don't care if I'm the villain
みんなと違うの当然だし
Being different from everyone is natural
あたしも変わらない
And I won't change
自由(ゆう)なままの自分
My own self, staying free
Oh everybody say
I want to be free
わがままなんて言わない
I won't say sweet things to my desires
それじゃ何も変えられない
If I do that, I can't change anything
Oh everybody say
I want to be free
わがままな自分公定
Deciding my own selfish way
生きているの私
I'm the one who's living
Oh...
ねえ 生きているんだ私
Hey, I'm really living
後悔ないように
So I have no regrets
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ
I've been choosing since I was born
思い出せ 私を私たらしめる
Remember what makes me, me
不確かなことなんて 何一つもない
There's not a single thing uncertain
嘘じゃない なりたい自分に
It's no lie, becoming who I want to be
好き 嫌い 常識 I don't care
Like it, hate it, common sense, I don't care
吹っ飛べ BANG!!!
Blow it up with a BANG!!!
好き 嫌い 常識 I don't care
Like it, hate it, common sense, I don't care
吹っ飛べ BANG!!!
Blow it up with a BANG!!!
震える手鳴らさ 手のひらで回さ
Ringing trembling hands, spinning them
分からす 挑発 下向いて舌打ち
Provocation, looking down, clicking tongue
からの HAHA
And then HAHA
Excuse me?
足からズバッ
Slicing from the legs
倍返し食らえ
Take it, double time!
パンチライン聴かせてあげる ah
Let me hear your punchline, ah
やってから考えなよ
Think after you do it
私がついてるから ah
Because I'm here with you, ah
Everybody say I want to be free
狂うこのビート 空 十戒
This beat goes crazy, Sky Ten Commandments
全部 黙らす show
Silence everything, it's a show
目醒ませよ kill it
Wake up and kill it
Wake up, wake up, get up, get up
ねぇ 聞いてんの?
Hey, are you listening?
ねぇ 聞いてんだろ?
Hey, you're listening, right?
生まれたその時から 選んできたんだ
I've been choosing since the moment I was born
思い出せ 私は私だ
Remember, I am myself
不可能なことなど 何一つもないさ じゃないの?
There's nothing impossible, isn't that right?
生まれたその時から 選んできたんだ
You've been choosing since the moment you were born
思い出せ あなたはあなただ
Remember, you are yourself
不可能なことなど 何一つもないさ じゃないの?
There's nothing impossible, isn't that right?
なりたい自分に
Into the person I want to be
好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹っ飛べ BANG!!!
Like it, hate it, common sense, I don't care - BANG!!!
流れてく時の中ででも
Even in the midst of flowing time,
倦怠さがほらグルグル回って
I feel languid, look, spinning around and around
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart leaving me
そう知らない
That's right, I don't know
自分から動くこともなく
Without even moving myself,
時の隙間に流され続けて
continuing to be swept away in the gaps of time
知らないわ 周りのことなど
I don't know about the things around me
私は私 それだけ
I am me, that's all
夢見てる なにも見てない
Dreaming, seeing nothing
語るも無駄な 自分の言葉
My own words, useless to even speak
悲しむなんて 疲れるだけよ
Grieving is just exhausting
なにも感じず 過ごせばいいの
It's fine to spend time feeling nothing
戸惑う言葉 与えられても
Even if given words that confuse,
自分の心 ただ上の空
my heart is just absent-minded
もし私から 動くのならば
If I were to move from myself,
すべて変えるのなら 黒にする
if everything were to change, I'd turn it black
こんな自分に 未来はあるの?
Is there a future for someone like me?
こんな世界に 私はいるの?
Am I in such a world?
今切ないの? 今悲しいの?
Am I in pain now? Am I sad now?
自分のことも 分からないまま
Without even knowing about myself
歩むことさえ 疲れるだけよ
Even walking is just exhausting
人のことなど 知りもしないわ
I don't even know about other people
こんな私も 変われるのなら
If even someone like me could change,
もし変われるのなら 白になる
if I could change, I'd turn white
流れてく時の中ででも
Even in the midst of flowing time,
倦怠さがほらグルグル回って
I feel languid, look, spinning around and around
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart leaving me
そう知らない
That's right, I don't know
自分から動くこともなく
Without even moving myself,
時の隙間に流され続けて
continuing to be swept away in the gaps of time
知らないわ 周りのことなど
I don't know about the things around me
私は私 それだけ
I am me, that's all
夢見てる なにも見てない
Dreaming, seeing nothing
語るも無駄な 自分の言葉
My own words, useless to even speak
悲しむなんて 疲れるだけよ
Grieving is just exhausting
動けよ
Move!
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
Should I just spend my time feeling nothing?
戸惑う言葉 与えられても
Even if I'm given confusing words...
自分の心 漂うだけなら
...if my heart is only drifting along...
もし私から動くのならば
If I were to move of my own accord...
すべて変えるのならば黒にする
...if I could change everything, I'd turn it all to black.
動くのならば 動くのならば
If I move, if I move...
すべて壊すわ すべて壊すわ
...I'll break everything, I'll break it all.
悲しむならば 悲しむならば
If I grieve, if I grieve...
私の心 白く変われる？
...can my heart turn white?
あなたのことも 私のことも
About you, about me...
すべてのことも まだ知らないの
...about everything, I still don't know.
重いまぶたを 開けたのならば
If I were to open my heavy eyelids...
すべて壊すのならば黒になれ
...if everything is to be broken, let it all turn to black.
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
Someday, the light of love you lit within your eyes...
時を超えて
...will transcend time...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
...and surely destroy the dreams...
確かに一つ壊すだろう
...of a world rushing toward ruin.
躊躇いを飲み干して
Drink down your hesitation.
君が望むモノは何？
What is it you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
In the path of such greedy longing,
儚い明日はあるの？
is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
The dream I had when I was a child,
古の魔法のように
like an ancient magic...
闇さえ砕く力で
...with the power to crush even the darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to see you smiling.
怯えるこの手の中には
Within these trembling hands,
手折られた花と勇気
are a plucked flower and courage.
想いだけが頼るすべて
My feelings are all I rely on,
光を呼び覚ます願い
a wish that awakens the light.
いつか君も誰かのために
Someday you too, for someone else's sake,
強い力を望むのだろう
will desire strong power.
愛が胸を捉えた夜に
On the night when love captured your heart,
未知の言葉が生まれてくる
unknown words will be born.
迷わずにゆけるなら
If I can go without hesitation,
心が砕けてもいいわ
it's okay even if my heart breaks.
いつも目前の悲しみに
Against the sorrow always before my eyes,
立ち向かうための呪文が欲しい
I want a spell to stand my ground.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are still a dreaming memory.
私は眠らない明日
I am the tomorrow that doesn't sleep.
二人が出会う奇跡を
The miracle of the two of us meeting—
勝ち取るために進むわ
I will move forward to win it.
怯えるこの手の中には
Within these trembling hands,
手折られた花と刃
are a plucked flower and a blade.
想いだけが生きるすべて
My feelings are everything I live for,
心に振りかざす願い
a wish held high in my heart.
あの日見た 太陽の輝く
The sunshine I saw that day...
不思議な国の本が好きだった頃
When I loved books about wonderlands...
願いはきっと叶うと教える おとぎ話を信じた
I believed in fairy tales telling me wishes come true.
光と影の中
In the light and shadow...
静かに咲き乱れていた
It was blooming quietly...
いにしえの魔法を優しく
The ancient magic, gently...
世界を変える力が
The power to change the world...
その手にあると囁く
Whispers that it's in your hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream an endless dream...
君と行く時の中で
Within the time I spend with you.
思いだけが生きる全て
My feelings are the only reason I live...
命を作るのは 願い
What creates life is a wish.
わーー！
Wooo!
アキちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Aki-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとう！イェーイ！
Thank you! Yay!
いや、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for coming today.
こちらこそですよ、呼んでくれてありがとう。
The pleasure is ours. Thanks for inviting us.
実はね、二人を呼んだのちょっと理由があって。
Actually, there's a reason why I invited you two.
おお？何だ何だ？
Oh? What is it, what is it?
前に、アキロゼの4周年の時に
Before, for my 4th anniversary,
三人で「Carabiner」っていう曲出させてもらったんだけど。
we released a song called "Carabiner" as a trio.
やりましたね！めちゃ良かったやつね！ハーモニーがね。
We did! That was a great one! The harmony...
もうね、ロボちゃんの歌も大好きだし、アイちゃんの歌も大好きだし...
I love Robo-chan's singing, and I love IRyS's singing...
そう、忘れられないの。わかる、わかる！めちゃわかる！
Yeah, I can't forget it. I know, I totally get it!
だからもう一回、このライブステージで三人で歌いたくて、今日は来てもらいました。
So I wanted to sing with the three of us on this stage again today.
嬉しい！ありがとう！
I'm so happy! Thank you!
そう、だからこれからは...これを機に、もっと何か三人で歌ったりとか
So from now on... with this as a start, I'd love to sing more as a trio,
何かそういうの挑戦できたらめちゃ嬉しい。
and try out new things together.
いいんですか？ハーモニーを重ねていきましょうよ！
Is that okay? Let's keep layering our harmonies!
ええ、いいの？嬉しい！三人で！ユニット名とか欲しいね！
Eh, really? I'm so glad! I want a unit name for us!
確かに欲しい！え、何だろうね？世界目指せるくらいのさ
Definitely! What should it be? A unit that can aim for the world...
ユニットにしてさ、世界のコンサートしようよ！
Let's do a world concert!
しましょうよ！世界に轟く、我らの何かをね、したいということで。
Let's! I want to do something that resonates across the world.
そう三人でライブとか、何かアコースティックとか、何かオーケストラライブとか！
Like a trio live, or acoustic, or an orchestra live!
うわー！え、良くないですか？そういうことをしてみたい！
Whoa! Isn't that great? I really want to try that!
我らならできるかもしれない！やろう！できる！お願いします！
We might be able to pull it off! Let's do it! We can!
あれ？え？これは一体何ですか？
Huh? Eh? What on earth is this?
お？もししかして...このライブでみんなからの、何かいいパワーで...
Oh? Could it be... with some kind of good power from everyone here...
何かいいパワー来た！儀式じゃん、それ！何だよそのパワー！
Some good power is coming! It's like a ritual! What's with that power!
こちらがなんと...完成しました！わー！何だそれ！
This has finally... been completed! Whoa! What's that!
実は...この後、アキロゼの新曲が...出ます！
Actually... after this, Akirose's new song... will be released!
わー！出た！きたー！
Whoa! It's out! It's here!
こちら、ま、今回のライブのテーマというか、壮大なテーマがあるんですけど。
This is like the theme of this live; it has a grand theme.
そちらも詰まったような楽曲になっています。
The song is packed with that theme.
そしてライブ終わりの日付が変わる時に、リリースしますので、ぜひ買って聴いてください！
It's releasing when the date changes after the live, so please listen to it!
いいね！みんな聴くぞー！
Nice! Everyone's gonna listen!
はい！ではでは次の曲にいきますか！次の曲！え、新曲お披露目？
Yes! Well then, shall we move to the next song? A new song reveal?
何だって？しちゃいます！わーー！
What's that? I'm doing it! Wooo!
もう新曲お披露目！え、今からってこと？
A new song reveal already! You mean right now?
今から！頑張ります！最後まで見逃せないですね！
Right now! I'll do my best! You can't miss a moment!
楽しみだ！アキちゃん頑張ってね！ありがとう！またね！
We're excited! Good luck, Aki-chan! Thank you! See you!
魅惑の言葉の裏面に忍ばせた
Hidden on the back of charming words
1mgのスパイス
A 1mg spice
たちまち華麗な指先で彩る
Instantly colored by brilliant fingertips
本日のダイス
Today's dice
当たり前見てた教室じゃ生き残れないでしょう
You can't survive in the classroom you took for granted
率直に言ってもう全てが欲しい
To be frank, I want it all now
独り勝ちオールイン
Solo victory, all-in
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
Doesn't matter what happens, right?
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, right?
翻弄して 翻弄されて ゾクゾク
Trifling, being trifled with, thrill after thrill
食らっちゃっても本望でしょ
It's what you wanted even if you take a hit, right?
最低だって化けるでしょ
Even at your worst, you'll transform, right?
見透かして 見透かされて 故に
See through, being seen through, and therefore...
終わりは無い
There is no end
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
All of this excitement is non-fiction
嗜むはずでもたまには飲み過ぎて
I meant to just enjoy it, but sometimes I drink too much
1回休み
One turn miss
周りもそわつく思わぬうたた寝で
Surroundings get restless as I drift into an unexpected nap
2回休み
Two turns miss
切れる頭と勘だけじゃ手に入らないモノ
Things you can't get with just a sharp mind and intuition
底で居て見下されるならいい
It's fine if I'm at the bottom and looked down upon
命懸けで楽しむわ
I'll enjoy it at the risk of my life
点と地は案外近くない？
Aren't heaven and earth surprisingly close?
この通り命懸け
Just like this, at the risk of my life
たかがモノポリーされど大勝利
It's just Monopoly, but nonetheless a grand victory
決める想い 今宵も私は強い
Determined feelings, tonight too, I am strong
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
Doesn't matter what happens, right?
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, right?
翻弄して 翻弄されて ゾクゾク
Trifling, being trifled with, thrill after thrill
食らっちゃっても本望でしょ
It's what you wanted even if you take a hit, right?
最低だって化けるでしょ
Even at your worst, you'll transform, right?
見透かして 見透かされて 故に
See through, being seen through, and therefore...
終わりは無い
There is no end
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
All of this excitement is non-fiction
堕ちても昇ってもノンフィクション
Falling or rising, it's non-fiction
中川に浮かぶ夕陽をめがけて
Aiming for the sunset floating on the Naka River
小石を蹴ったら靴まで飛んで
I kicked a pebble and even my shoe flew off
ジョギングしていた大工の頭に
Hitting the head of a jogging carpenter
ガキのまんまだと笑われたのさ
I was laughed at for still being a brat
どこかに元気を落っことしても
Even if I drop my spirits somewhere
葛飾亀有アクビをひとつ
Katsushika, Kameari, a single yawn
変わらない町並み妙に優しいよ
The unchanging cityscape is strangely kind
中央広場で子供の手を引く
In the central square, holding a child's hand
太ったあの娘は幼なじみ
That chubby girl is my childhood friend
ゴンパチ行こうぜ わたしゃフラれた
Let's go to Gonpachi, I got dumped
今も想ってるとからかわれたよ
I was teased that I still have feelings
何もいいことなかったけれど
Though nothing good happened
葛飾水元 流れる雲と
Katsushika, Mizumoto, with the drifting clouds
ラプソディー口ずさみ 少し歩こうか
Humming a rhapsody, shall we walk a bit?
カラスがなくからもう日が暮れるね
The crows are cawing, so the sun is setting
焼き鳥ほうばりビール飲もうか
Shall we stuff ourselves with yakitori and drink beer?
トンガリ帽子の取水塔から
From the intake tower with a pointed hat
帝釈天へと夕陽が落ちる
The sun sets towards Taishakuten
明日もこうして終わるんだね
I guess tomorrow will end like this too
隠し隠しはまた 幸せだって
Hiding and hiding, but saying I'm happy again
隠して気が付いた
I hid it and then I realized...
馬鹿な女だから
Because I'm a foolish woman
どこかに元気を落としても
Even if I lose my energy somewhere
隠しかめあり あくびをひとつ
With a hidden turtle, I let out a yawn
変わらない街並みが 妙に優しいや
The unchanging cityscape is strangely kind
アキロゼ生誕祭2026をご覧の皆さん、いかがでしたでしょうか？
Everyone watching AkiRose Birthday 2026, how did you like it?
さて、ここからは大事なお知らせがあるんで、最後までしっかり聞いていってね！
Now, I have some important news, so please listen carefully until the end!
まずは、お知らせ1つ目！
First, the first announcement!
アキ・ローゼンタール2026誕生日グッズ発売です！
Aki Rosenthal 2026 birthday merchandise is now on sale!
今回は、ライブの世界観をギュッと楽しんでもらえるグッズを頑張って制作いたしました。
This time, we worked hard to create goods that allow you to fully enjoy the live concert's world.
なので、今回のライブが良かったなーって思った方は、ぜひ応援で購入していただくのもすごく嬉しいです！
So, if you thought this live concert was great, I'd be very happy if you'd support me by purchasing them!
それでは、まず1つ目のグッズ！
Now, for the first item!
Life is GAME ラバーマット！
Life is GAME Rubber Mat!
今回のイラストはLAM先生に描き下ろしていただきました。素敵なイラストありがとうございます！
This illustration was drawn by LAM-sensei. Thank you for the wonderful illustration!
今回のライブの世界観をイメージしたイラストになっています。
The illustration is based on the world of this live concert.
めちゃくちゃセクシーで色っぽいけどカッコいいようなアキロゼになっています。
It shows an AkiRose who is incredibly sexy and alluring, yet also cool.
ラバーマットで思う存分楽しんでください。
Please enjoy it to your heart's content with the rubber mat.
ちなみにサイズはカードゲームにぴったり。
By the way, the size is perfect for card games.
この意味わかるよね？
You know what that means, right?
2つ目のグッズが、
The second item is...
運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット！
The Fated 5 Cards - Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set!
アキロゼがあなたのことを占って背中を押してあげます。
AkiRose will tell your fortune and give you a push forward.
1日の始まりや、何か運命を託したい…みたいなそんな時に使って楽しむ。
Use it to have fun at the start of your day, or when you want to leave something to fate.
そして、5枚バーンって飾っておけるので、見ても楽しめるようになっています。
And since you can display all five cards together, they're enjoyable just to look at.
占い方法は、この後紹介するアキロゼのASMRボイスと連動しております。
The fortune-telling method is linked with AkiRose's ASMR voice, which I'll introduce next.
飾っても楽しい、使っても楽しい。そのような連動グッズになっているので、ぜひゲットしてください！
Fun to display, fun to use. It's a linked item like that, so please get one!
続いてのグッズは、
The next item is...
アキロゼのトランプ！
AkiRose's Playing Cards!
作っちゃいました！ふふふっ。
I went and made them! Hehe.
こちら実際に遊んでいただけるトランプなので、
These are playing cards you can actually play with, so...
たくさん予備も買ったほうがいいんじゃないかなーと思います。
I think it might be a good idea to buy lots of spares.
ぜひトランプでもアキロゼをたくさん楽しんで、アピールもしてくださいね。
Please enjoy AkiRose through the cards and show them off, too.
続いては、こちら。
Next is this.
アキロゼのカードケース！
AkiRose's Card Case!
このカードはもちろんトランプなど小物入れても大丈夫です。
You can use it for these cards, or of course, for playing cards and other small items.
ぜひお家や持ち歩きに使ってね。
Please use it at home or take it with you.
そして、ボイスの紹介です！
And now for the voices!
今回もASMRボイスを特別に発売！
We're releasing special ASMR voices again this time!
アキとロゼがそれぞれ左右からあなたのことを誘惑しちゃうかも。
Aki and Rose might tempt you from both left and right.
台本も頑張って書いたので、ぜひぜひたっぷり楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I worked hard on the script, so I'd be happy if you enjoyed it to the fullest.
こちらボイスは「Life is GAME アキとロゼの晩餐」。
This voice is titled 'Life is GAME: Dinner with Aki and Rose'.
こちらをメインとし、ASMRショートボイスとして、先ほどの運命の5枚タロット風アクリルカードと連動したショートボイスが入っております。
That's the main part, and as ASMR short voices, we have clips linked with the Fated 5 Tarot-style Acrylic Cards.
ショートボイスのシャッフルランダム再生をして選ばれたボイスが、
The voice that plays when you use shuffle random playback...
あなたの運命の1枚になります。
...will become your 'one card of destiny'.
ぜひいろいろ楽しんでね！
Please enjoy it in various ways!
これらのグッズすべてが詰まったフルセット購入には、なんと特典も付いております。
And there's even a special bonus for purchasing the full set, which includes all these goods!
今回のキービジュアルのイラストを使ったチケット風カードになっております。
It's a ticket-style card using this time's key visual illustration.
あなたはこのゲームに参加する？参加しない？
Will you participate in this game? Or not?
こちらもライブの世界観を高めるアイテムになっているので、ぜひゲットしてください！
This is also an item to enhance the live concert's world, so please get one!
そして、数量限定あります！
And there's a limited quantity available!
直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ったものになっております。頑張って書きます！
It includes a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped duplicated message. I'll do my best to write them!
そして、数量限定が終わり次第、箔押しでの複製サインとメッセージが入ったチケット風カードになります。
Once the limited quantity is gone, it will be a ticket-style card with a foil-stamped duplicated signature and message.
ぜひフルセット購入特典ゲットしてね！
Please get the full set purchase bonus!
大事な発売時間は、この後21時30分！
The important release time is 21:30, right after this!
21時30分にショップオープンです！ぜひ登録など準備して備えておいてね。
The shop opens at 21:30! Please get ready by registering and all that.
続きまして、お知らせ2つ目！
Moving on, the second announcement!
この後、21時45分からメンバー限定のアフターライブを行います！
Starting at 21:45, we'll be having a member-only after-live event!
ライブ本編とはまた違う楽曲を披露する予定なので、ぜひお楽しみに！
I plan to perform different songs from the main live, so look forward to it!
今日メンバーになった方もぜひぜひ見てね！
Even those who became members today, please come and watch!
ちなみに、過去のライブのメンバー限定アフターライブも見れちゃうと思うので、ぜひその...
By the way, I think you can also watch member-only after-lives from past concerts, so please...
あちらも見てみてね
Please check that out too.
ちなみに今回のサムネイルイラストは メンバー限定で 壁紙として プレゼント予定です
By the way, this thumbnail illustration will be given as a wallpaper to members only.
お楽しみに
Look forward to it!
そして お知らせ 3つ目
And now for the third announcement.
本日の 生誕祭ライブの後も お楽しみは まだまだ続きます
The fun continues even after today's birthday live!
なんと ホロアースにて 特別企画 アキロゼ生誕祭 アンコール in ホロアースを 開催します
A special project, 'Aki Rose Birthday Encore in HoloEarth', will be held!
今回 初披露した 新曲「モノポリー」を ホロアースで 歌っちゃいます
I'll be singing my new song 'Monopoly', performed for the first time today, in HoloEarth.
いろんな角度から アキロゼのパフォーマンスや 演出を じっくりと 見てみてくださいね
Please take a close look at AkiRose's performance and production from various angles.
さらに ホロアースだけの MCパートも たっぷりあるので ぜひぜひ 会いに来てください
There will also be plenty of MC parts exclusive to HoloEarth, so please come see me.
開催日は 3月13日 3月13日です
The event date is March 13th. It's March 13th!
詳細は ホロアース公式Xを チェックしてね
Check the official HoloEarth X for details.
そして 最後のお知らせが
And the final announcement is...
新曲「モノポリー」
New song, 'Monopoly'!
本日 日付が変わる頃に リリースされますので 各音楽配信サービスから ぜひ 購入してね
It will be released at midnight tonight, so please buy it from music streaming services.
たくさん聴いてね
Please listen to it a lot!
振り付けも 歌も とってもキャッチーなので 覚えてみんなで楽しんでもらえる 愛されるような楽曲に なってくれたら 嬉しいなって 思っています
The choreography and song are very catchy, so I hope it becomes a beloved song that everyone enjoys.
また後日 ライブ配信で 新曲「モノポリー」だったり 今回のライブに触れた 後日談など 語ったり 一緒に見たりなど したいなと思ってるので
In a future stream, I'd like to talk about 'Monopoly', share behind-the-scenes stories, and watch this live together.
ぜひ チャンネル登録 高評価ぽち 通知もオン! してるって人は 今ぽちっとしてね
So please subscribe, give a thumbs up, and turn on notifications! If you haven't yet, do it now.
絶対絶対 また会いに来てね
Be sure to come see me again!
それでは
And now...
運命は 時に残酷
Fate is cruel at times.
あなたが選びたくて 選んだものではないかもしれない
It may not be what you chose because you wanted to.
だけど いつでも あなたの人生は あなたのもの
But your life is always yours.
人生は一度きり
You only live once.
やり直しの効かない このゲーム
In this game where there are no do-overs...
あなたは どう楽しむ?
...how will you enjoy it?
【主催者】 アキ・ローゼンタール
[Organizer] Aki Rosenthal
【出演者】 赤見かるび 天鬼ぷるる ズズ 律可
[Performers] Akami Karubi, Amaki Pururu, Zuzu, Rikka
癒月ちょこ 森カリオペ 鷹嶺ルイ IRyS
Yuzuki Choco, Mori Calliope, Takane Lui, IRyS
水宮枢 AZKi 大神ミオ
Mizumiya Kururu, AZKi, Ookami Mio
【歌唱ゲスト】 かしわねこ dtto. げつん
[Singing Guests] Kashiwaneko, dtto., Getsun
アルランディス おおはらMEN
Aruran-disu, Ohara MEN
だいだら marunnn Axel Syrios
Daidara, marunnn, Axel Syrios
甘狼このみ 群青ロマン 那和ツムグ
Amagami Konomi, Gunjou Roman, Nawa Tsumugu
梟雄しろや かんせる たちばな
Kyouyuu Shiroya, Cansel, Tachibana
狂蘭メロコ 水無瀬 わきを
Meloco Kyoran, Minase, Wakiwo
ろぜっぴん しろまんた 歌衣メイカ
Rose-pin, Shiromanta, Utai Meika
花ノ木まる おなつのにびたし Middleeetv
Hananoki Maru, Onatsu no Nibitashi, Middleeetv
ゆう。 シード 荒咬オウガ
Yuu, Seed, Aragami Oga
ドンピシャ ひぐち!ひぐち! 如月れん
Donpisha, Higuchi! Higuchi!, Kisaragi Ren
玉餅かずよ ロボ子さん まぎー3
Tamamochi Kazuyo, Roboco-san, Maggie 3
ととみっくす 渋谷ハル 日ノ隈らん
Totomix, Shibuya Hal, Hinokuma Ran
猫汰つな 秋雪こはく 白雪レイド
Nekota Tsuna, Syusetu Kohaku, Shirayuki Raid
【振付制作】 ミユキニシジマ
[Choreography] Miyuki Nishijima
【バックダンサー】 高橋千里 RISAKO Mishio Tokita Shiopen
[Backup Dancers] Chisato Takahashi, RISAKO, Mishio Tokita, Shiopen
【サムネイルイラスト】 澄夜 咲星
[Thumbnail Illustration] Sumiya Sakuse
【ロゴ制作】 柊椋
[Logo Design] Hiiragi Muku
【モノポリー ジャケットイラスト】 しまぐち ニケ
['Monopoly' Jacket Illustration] Shimaguchi Nike
【モノポリー ジャケットロゴ】 ミナトデザイン
['Monopoly' Jacket Logo] Minato Design
【音源制作】 トライフロンティア合同会社 クックルP
[Music Production] Tri-Frontier LLC, Cukkul P
夜湾/yowan. Sumia 夢魅たび ジョウコウ 宮内椋太 山本こーすけ
Yowan, Sumia, Yumemi Tabi, Joukou, Ryouta Miyauchi, Kohsuke Yamamoto
合同会社 VESSEL LIFE sa-sara SAZA
VESSEL LIFE LLC, sa-sara, SAZA
株式会社音響ハウス 大島健志 内柴海
Onkyo Haus Inc., Kenji Oshima, Kai Uchishiba
山内翔平 呂承勳 宮本創平 青木未来 内田日和 竹田壮志 中内茂治 山田涼也
Shohei Yamauchi, Ro Shokun, Sohei Miyamoto, Miku Aoki, Hiyori Uchida, Soushi Takeda, Shigeharu Nakauchi, Ryoya Yamada
【背景 / OL映像制作】 ぺたぺた U 茶人百 (スタジオメイビー)
[Background / OL Video Production] Petapeta, U, Chajinhyaku (Studio Maybe)
Quma H!B!K! ななせむぎ りずにか Nザミー 堕地るん ゆーせき YuumA ぽぞく
Quma, H!B!K!, Nanasemugi, Rizunica, N-Zummy, Ochirun, Yuseki, YuumA, Pozoku
【OP制作】 ぺたぺた 茶人百 野村生誕 (スタジオメイビー) ぽぞく
[OP Production] Petapeta, Chajinhyaku, Nomura Seitan (Studio Maybe), Pozoku
【Special Thanks】 ロゼ隊 ALL STAFF and You
[Special Thanks] Rosetai, ALL STAFF and You
最後まで 楽しんでくれて 本当に ありがとう
Thank you so much for enjoying until the very end.
また 最高の 景色 見に行こうね
Let's go see the best scenery again together.
それじゃあ
Well then...
バイバイ!
Bye-bye!